[{"answer": "What did you find", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Touchstone.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Present company excluded of course", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Touchstone.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Hello, my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Teal'c, it's good to see you are well", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Touchstone.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Well, that's interesting. Is there something I can do for you, Colonel my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I remember a reference to it, but correct me if I'm wrong, nothing came back from the survey", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Touchstone.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Another SGC team", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Who's pulling the strings, my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Touchstone.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Drop it ", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "The link is gone. They destroyed the MALP", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Touchstone.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Didn't have time for a full triangulation, but we've got it narrowed down", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "How far down", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Touchstone.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh well, that place", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Two things. Who's got the Stargate? Who's got the weather device", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Touchstone.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I don't have time for games, my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "That doesn't sound like a good thing", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Touchstone.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "my friend, if it were military, I'd know about it. It's got to be civilian", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend, if it were military, I'd know about it. It's got to be civilian", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Touchstone.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "There's always something going on at that place, and most of the time it's strange. But nothing about a Stargate or a weather thingy. Hey! Does this have something to do with all the weird weather lately", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Anything strange going on at that place", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Touchstone.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "How about Southern that place? Heard about anything going on there", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "They've come back uncle my friend! Just as I told you", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Touchstone.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "They do", "qsentId": 24}]